A Guide to the WRVA Radio Collection, 1925-2000
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Photographs 1925-2000 (Box Boxes 33-66 and Negative Boxes 1-14)
  - Subseries C: Negatives (Box 1-10)
    - Frank Brooks at Azalea Mall Remote in a trailer, Nov. 22, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Gloria Bartley at High's Plantation Room, Southside Plaza, Feb. 27, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Benjamin Moore Paint Can, Aug. 11, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks Billboards, April 10 - July 1 1959, Dec. 10 1959 - Jan. 10, 1960, 4 sleeves (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Campus Lane Clothes in Greentree's Window, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks - Election night, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Maynard Ferguson at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 21, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Florsheim shoes in Greentree's, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks and Wilbur M. Gaunt, Jr., Executive Director of the Virginia Retail Council, on "Open for Opinion", Mar. 23, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Henry R. Gonner, Central Richmond Association, Mar. 12, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks at High's Plantation Room, Southside Plaza, Feb. 27, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Frances Hollans at the Organ, 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 22, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Interwoven socks in Greentree's window, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks at Jaycee's Carnival Winter Garden, Hotel Richmond, with engineer Dick Tisdale, Apr. 15, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Kai Winding, Mar. 11, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks - Miller and Rhoads Remote, Oct. 14, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks at N. F. Jacobs Remote, Nov. 26, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks - "Pal Joey" Promotion at State Theatre, Dec. 21, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks (right) with Cy Rains (center) and Dick Tisdale (left) at High's Plantation Room, Southside Plaza, Feb. 27, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with J. Linwood Rice, Public relations counsel for 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Mayor Mrs. Eleanor P. Sheppard, July 26, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks in Thalhimers' Window with engineer Ed Hines, May 22, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks TV spot, May 7, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Frank Brooks with Van Heusen shirts in Greentree's, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Brown, Robert (Box 2)
    - S. A. Burnette (left), Henrico County Board of Supervisors candidate, with Jack Clements, May 11, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Bus Card (VTC) Special Demonstration by Temple Cook and Bill Kindle, Jan. 14, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Bus Dash Signs, Richmond and Norfolk - Norfolk Billboard - WRVA - WRVC (I-II), 2 sleeves (Box 2)
    - Business - Education Day (Box 2)
    - Byrd, Senator Harry F. (Box 2)
    - Byrd, Harry F., Jr. (Box 2)
    - Byrnes, Gov. James F. - Visit to Williamsburg session of 1952 Virginia General Assembly (Box 2)
    - Chris Cabell (William Cabell Venable) at microphone (Box 2)
    - Cadillac Dog Food Banquet, Southside Plaza, Nov. 11, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Cadillac Dog Food Window Display, Oct. 15, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Cadillac Dog Food on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Calling All Cooks (I-IV), 4 sleeves (Box 2)
    - Call, Norman - President, RF&P Railroad (Box 2)
    - Camel Cigarettes Window Display, July 20, 1960 (Box 2)
    - "Capitol Squirrel" - copies of art work used for 1960 Douglas Southall Freeman Award Entry ("Annexation or Merger", "Flood Control", "Police Probe", "Politics"), Sept. 1960 (Box 2)
    - "Capitol Squirrel" - 11th Tobacco Festival Parade (Box 2)
    - Carey, Sam (Box 2)
    - Carlson, Arthur (Box 2)
    - Mary Elizabeth Carter with balloon at Southside Plaza Shopping Center, Oct. 13, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Mary Alice Carter with Kathleen Heinz at Southside Plaza Shopping Center (with balloons), Oct. 13, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Mary Carter with Phil Jordan "Yardstick Promotion", Mar. 18, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Hazel Caulden, Jan. 12, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Cessna Homes Theatre Marquee, Sept. 1, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Chap-Ans Window Display, Dec. 19, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Chapstick and Chap-ans on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Dec. 15, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Chezik, Ted (Box 2)
    - Christmas Party in the WRVA Theatre, Dec. 21, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Christmas Parties - WRVA (Box 2)
    - Churchill, Sarah, and Virginius Dabney and William B. Thalhimer, Jr. (Box 2)
    - Clarke, Herb (Box 2)
    - Class Room 59 (new radio series) - Houghton Mifflin Co. Window Display, Feb. 10, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements - 1958 Virginia Associated Press Broadcasters Awards, National Press Club, Washington, D.C. (L-R: Frank Wilson, Jack Clements, Max Fullerton, Chief of AP Bureau, Baltimore, Harry Monroe, and Bob Smith), May 2, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements at beeper recorder, Apr. 30, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements Billboards, Feb. 2, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Clements - Bishop - Wilson - Tisdale at opening of General Assembly (taken in Capitol Gallery), Jan. 8, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Walter Bishop at Patrick Henry Airport for Queen Elizabeth's visit to Jamestown and Williamsburg, Oct. 16, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Walter Bishop on Election Night, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with (L-R) Dewey Brazzel, Richmond Sales Manager for Purina; Bobby Shaw, Rt. 4, Glen Allen, Virginia; Russell O. Berry, Holzgrefe Brothers Hathery, June 20, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements at College of William and Mary at Wren Building for Queen Elizabeth's visit to Jamestown and Williamsburg with engineer Dick Tisdale, Oct. 16, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with McCarthy Downs, Jr., candidate for Henrico County Board of Supervisors, June 3, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements - Election Night, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements - J. Vaughan Gary Election, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Cecil Harper, candidate for Henrico County Board of Supervisors, June 10, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Leo Hoarty of WBDF, Virginia Beach - Installation of Clements as president, Virginia Associated Press Broadcasters at National Press Club in Washington, D.C., May 2, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements interview at 1959 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 29, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Ledford, candidate for Henrico County Board of Supervisors, June 17, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements makes a call from the mobile news unit, May 1, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with member of cast of the "Happiest Millionaire" - Jaycee's Carnival, Winter Garden, Hotel Richmond, Apr. 15, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements at microphone in Studio "B" with telephone, May 1, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with "Miss Virginia of 1958", Miss Barbara Doris Guthrie of Martinsville, Virginia, Aug. 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Miss Virginia, Aug. 24, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Mobile News Unit (pointing to location of Radio Telephone), May 1, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Mobile Studio "Back to School Safety Month", Sept. 1, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Clements, Monroe, and Aaroe at Virginia Associated Press Broadcasters Awards Presentation, Mar. 29, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Clements - Monroe Billboard on U.S. Route #1 North, Aug. 22, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements at Moto-Mower Contest, June 10, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with newsroom clip file, May 1, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements at newsroom typewriter, May 1, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Ted Partlow, Lee Wicker, Bob Portteu (Polariod Corp.) in Galeski Photo Center, Feb. 6, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements - Passport Photos, Feb. 18, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Tollie H. Quinn, candidate for Henrico County Board of Supervisors, June 24, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Buddy Ragsdale, candidate for Henrico County Board of Supervisors, July 1, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements Remote, Aug. 27, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Schemerhorn, candidate for Henrico County Board of Supervisors, May 21, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Bobby Shaw, 1st place 4-H Junior Broiler Growers, June 20, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Nicholas Spinnella, president of St. Bridget's PTA, winners of "Apple for the Teacher" contest, Mar. 15, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with stripteaser at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 22, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements in Thalhimers' Window with engineer Dick Tisdale, May 21, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements - TV News spot, May 8, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements with Two Thalhimers Models on "Sideview on the News", May 19, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements at UP Machine, Oct. 10, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Jack Clements and Frank Wilson in Mobile News Unit, May 1, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Coldene Lobby Display, Jan. 31, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Coldene Window Display, Jan. 31, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Comet on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Apr. 19, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Colonial Stores on WRVA Theatre Marquee, June 7, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Dr. Ernest L. Copley - Pulling of his body from James River, May 13, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Corn Chex Window Display, Oct. 30, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Corn Chex on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Nov. 2, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Kitty Cousins (Box 3)
    - Walter F. Craigie, President of Central Richmond Association, at Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Opening, June 30, 1958 (Box 3)
    - George Creegan Puppet Show at Tuckahoe Fire Station, Dec. 7, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Crippled Children's Hospital, Dec. 30, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Crippled Children's Hospital Appreciation Awards - 6 year old Michael Gray makes presentation, Feb. 4, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Crippled Children's Hospital Appreciation Awards (L-R: Mrs. Paul Erdman; John B. Tansey; R. Karleen Ingerson; Mrs. A. Wade Lamb, Jr.; A. Churchill Young, Jr.; Dr. James T. Tucker, MD), Feb. 4, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Dale Crisp (left) and Sherry Eborn in Tobacco Festival Parade, Oct. 4, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Crosby, Bing (Box 3)
    - Crowder, J. B. D. (Box 3)
    - Darcel, Denise (Box 3)
    - Day, Gene (Box 3)
    - D-Con on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Mar. 29, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean in Derby Hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean - Election Night 1957, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean Gag Shots, Mar. 18, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean with Audrey Gill, Virginia Farm Queen of 1961, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean Head Shots, Mar. 12, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean in Mobile Studio at Virginia Sports Cars on West Broad (first remote with trailer), Aug. 14, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean Portraits, Aug. 1963 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean - TV Promotion Spot, May 7, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Lou Dean at Ward's TV and Appliance Center, 1806 W. Broad, Mar. 14, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Derby Hat Promotion with Greentree's, Apr. 22, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Derby Hat Promotion with Greentree's (L-R: Frank Brooks, Lou Dean, Lyle Bradley, Bob Smith, Bob McHone, Alden Aaroe), Apr. 22, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Derby Hat Promotion (Box 3)
    - Derby, Robert L. (Box 3)
    - Dogwood Knoll Homes Window Display, Oct. 6, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Dogwood Knoll Homes on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Aug 14, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Dominion Chevrolet on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Jan. 19, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Dominion Chevrolet on WRVA Theatre Marquee, May 29, 1961 (Box 3)
    - John Driver at Microphone, Sept. 20, [?] (Box 3)
    - Dubose Buick 1959 Car Preview Night, Sept. 19, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Dubose, J. Edwin (Box 3)
    - Duke's Mayonnaise Lobby Display with Sarah Jane Grogan and Ralph Krueger, June 13 - July 1958 (Box 3)
    - Duke's Mayonnaise Window Display, June 13 - July 1958 (Box 3)
    - Duke's Mayonnaise - Wood's Market, Aug. 21, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Bill Duncan in derby hat, Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Durden, Chauncy - receiving Barber Poll Award from Ray Kennedy (Box 3)
    - Eagles, Nellie (Box 3)
    - Easter Bonnet Contest Winners, Apr. 3, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Easter Bonnet Contest Winners (rejects), Apr. 3, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Easter Bonnet Contest Winners, Apr. 14, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (I-II), 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Election Central (Box 3)
    - Election Coverage (Box 3)
    - Election Coverage, Nov. 7, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Election Coverage - WRVA Radio and TV in Theatre (I-IV), Nov. 8, 1960, 4 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Election Night - Councilmatic Election (I-II), June 10, 1958, 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Election Scenes, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 3)
    - "Eleven-Forty" 1140 Family Contest at City Stadium, Apr. 21, 1967 (Box 3)
    - Miss Eskimo Pie, Miriam P. Molander, at Willow Lawn (I-II), Apr. 10, 1963, 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Miss Eskimo Pie, Miriam P. Molander, at Willow Lawn with Irby Hollans, Joe Lowen, and Ralph Krueger, Apr. 11, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Miss Eskimo Pie, Miriam P. Molander, in WRVA-Radio Studio Display, Apr. 11, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Eskimo Pie Promotion with Mrs. Anne Garrett, July 27, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Esskay Meats on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Mar. 15, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Esso Bumper Strips "Your Esso Reporter" on Red Top Cabs, Apr. 15 - May 31, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Esso Conference Luncheon at the Rotunda Club (L-R: John Tansey; Roy E. McDaniel, Manager of Virginia-West Virginia Division of Esso; Walter Bishop; Jack Clements; C. Graham Pembroke; General Sales Manager; Hal Barre; Carroll F. Toler, Merchandise Manager; James Irving Robertson, Assistant to McDaniel), Nov. 5, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Esso Display at 1959 State Fair of Virginia, Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Esso Display "Your Esso Reporter" at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Esso - "Prize-O-Rama" meeting of dealers at Jefferson Hotel with Jack Clements and Lon Backman, Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Esso Reporter on WRVA Theatre Marquee, July 3, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Esso Standard Oil Company Billboards, Aug. 1, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Esso - WRVA Luncheon at the Commonwealth Club, Nov. 5, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Esso - "Your Esso Reporter" on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Aug. 4-29, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Esso - "Your Esso Reporter" on WRVA Theatre Marquee, May 7, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Evans, Mark (Box 3)
    - Eveready Batteries on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Dec. 22, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Fab Soap Displays at Giant Food Stores, May 22, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., with Edith Lindeman (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 with Army, Navy, and Marine Units, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen, 1961 - cuts ribbon to open State Fair of 1961, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 - Miss Audrey Gill, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 - Miss Audrey Gill at 4-H Tractor Drivers Contest, Sept. 26, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 - Miss Audrey Gill with Alden Aaroe, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 receives trophy (L-R: Admiral Glover, Paul Sanders, Miss Audrey Gill, Mrs. S. Frank Carr), Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 with State Fair Officials (L-R: Paul Sanders, Mrs. Sheppardson, Mrs. Frank Carr, Paul Brinkley, Miss Audrey Gill, Colonel Hancock Reed, Alden Aaroe, Sam Bemiss, Admiral Glover), Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 with Virginia Electric Cooperatives Display, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1961 with Virginia Federation of Home Demonstration Clubs, Sept. 22, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen Contest of 1963 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen Contest of 1964 (I-III), Sept. 12, 1964, 3 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1963 - Opening State Fair, Sept. 20, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1963 - Dixie Perkins on "Governor's Day", Sept. 24, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1963 - Dixie Perkins with Donna Ratcliff, "Miss State Fair 1962" and Lisa Hanmer, "Miss State Fair 1963", Sept. 22, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1964 - Linda Carole Beard at Governor's Day with winner of 4-H tractor contest and Miss State Fair, Brenda Ann Lewis of Fredericksburg (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1964 - Linda Carole Beard at Miss State Fair Contest, Sept. 27, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Farm Queen of 1964 - Linda Carole Beard opens state fair, Sept. 25, 1964 (Box 3)
    - F.C.C. Measuring Point, July 24, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Mrs. Fearnow's Brunswick Stew on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Dec. 1, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Federal Office Building Ground Breaking Ceremony sponsored by Central Richmond Association with Senator A. Willis Robertson, Mayor A. Scott Anderson, etc., June 15, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Feen-A-Mint / Chooz Lobby Display (I-II), Jan. 14, 1958, 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Ferko String Band on Hotel Richmond Steps for Tobacco Festival, Oct. 24, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Findlay, Dave (I-II), 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Flako Pie Crust at Evans Supermarket, 34th and E. Marshall - "Lewis Martin Week", Oct. 24, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Flako Pie Crust Mix at Stratford Hills Supermarket, Nov. 21, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Senator Ralph E. Flanders (R - Vermont) at Engineers-Scientist Dinner with J. Louis Reynolds on left, at John Marshall, Feb. 21, 1958 (Box 3)
    - FLIT on WRVA Theatre Marquee, May 25, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Football Billboards, Oct. 2, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Football on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Sept. 14, 1959 (Box 3)
    - Ford, H. A. (Box 3)
    - Foster, L. C. (Box 3)
    - Four-Way Cold Tablets Window Display (I-II), Mar. 8, 1958, 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Fouts, J. Sam (Box 3)
    - Franklin, Harold (Box 3)
    - Bill Freeland (I-II), Nov. 20, 1957, 2 sleeves (Box 3)
    - Bill Freeland Gag Shots, Nov. 20, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Bill Freeland Head Shots, Mar. 12, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Free Wax on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Oct. 27, 1959 (Box 3)
    - French Merci Train Officials (Box 3)
    - Mayor F. Henry Garber at Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Opening, June 30, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Mrs. Anne Garrett for Eskimo Pie Promotion with Mr. and Mrs. Vernon Davis, July 27, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Garrett, Patsy (Box 4)
    - Garthright, Mike (Box 4)
    - Mike Garthright and Ed Hines in WRVA Master Control Election, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 4)
    - General Assembly - Governor Thomas B. Stanley Addresses Joint Session, Jan. 8, 1958 (Box 4)
    - General Assembly Opening, 1954 (Box 4)
    - George, W. Brooks (Box 4)
    - Georgia Mountain Boys, Apr. 30, 1957 (Box 4)
    - General Oil Company on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Feb. 2, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Giant Food Stores - "Lewis Martin Week," May 22, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Gill, Josephine (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis, Walter Bishop, and Tom Carlin, "Colonel Virginia" - 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 20, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis (center), Major Burton (right) of Esso, and Paul Jolly (left) of Esso, Dec. 5, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis with Charlottesville Chamber of Commerce Executive, Jan. 1961 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis and David Kilgore - "The Barksdale Players", Jan. 30, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis and Henry Meacham of Dun & Bradstreet (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis with Robert Porterfield, Chairman 1958 Cancer Crusade, June 12, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis with Paula Prentis (right), Dec. 13, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis with two girls (Gloria Sheehan on left), Oct. 1960 (Box 4)
    - Dick Gillis with Bill Willis of Henrico Herald, Jan. 17, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Richard S. Gillis, Virginia State Chamber of Commerce at 1957 State Fair, Sept. 21, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Bob Gilmore's Car with Vee's signs, July 7, 1964 (Box 4)
    - Bob Gilmore with Romeo Champagne, owner of Richmond Virginians and Lou Martin, Business Manager (Box 4)
    - Bob Gilmore and John Harmon in baseball get-up (Box 4)
    - Bob Gilmore and John Harmon with microphone (Box 4)
    - Bob Gilmore and John Harmon (black out shots) (Box 4)
    - Bob Gilmore - Portrait with microphone (Box 4)
    - Glinn, Emma (Box 4)
    - Miss Emma Glinn, Receptionist, Feb. 3, 1958 (Box 4)
    - GMAC signs in office, June 12, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Godfrey, Arthur with Sunshine Sue, Mrs. Godfrey, and Governor William Tuck (Box 4)
    - Golden Garbage Can Award, awarded by City Manager Horace Edwards to the team of Page, Clarke, and Wiltshire, Nov. 16, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Good Manners (Box 4)
    - Gosden, Freeman (Amos) with C. T. Lucy (Box 4)
    - Graham, Bill in WRVA Theatre, May 8, 1956 (Box 4)
    - Dean C. J. Gray - Scholarship Quiz at Albemarle High School near Charlottesville, Feb. 12, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Dean C. J. Gray, University of Richmond, Feb. 10, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Greece's King and Queen (Box 4)
    - Greentree's Remote - watching Alden Aaroe and Miss Virginia, Nov. 17, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Greentree's Window Display in Snack Bar, Nov. 12, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Greentree's window at night remote broadcasts, Nov. 20, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation and Atlantic Life Insurance Co. on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Sept. 20, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Gulf Oil Corp. window display, Aug. 21, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Gulf Oil Corp. on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Aug. 10, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Gulf Oil Corp. on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Aug. 24, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Gulf Oil - service station poster display (station is at Lombardy Street and Chamberlayne Ave.), Oct. 23, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Gulf Scoreboard 1962 Football Season, Oct. 30, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Jan Hagel Cookies on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Nov. 6, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Jan Hagel Cookie on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Nov. 3-7, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Jan Hagel Cookies given at New Dominion Barn Dance by Lee Wicker, Nov. 22, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Hamilton, Fred (Box 4)
    - Wade Hanky at Tobacco Festival Opening Dance in Arena with Tommy Dorsey Orchestra, Sept. 22, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Hardee's Drive-In Trailer Remote, Apr. 20, 1962 (Box 4)
    - John Harmon at microphone, Apr. 13, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Governor Albertis S. Harrison at WRVA-Radio microphone, Mar. 14, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Jack Harter at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 20, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Jack Harter and Harold Phillips at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 20, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Jack Harter Portrait shot, Mar. 18, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Bob Hatcher at Ampex Tape Recorder Racks, Oct. 10, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Bob Hatcher and Hal Phillips at Tape Rack on Election Night feeding Jack Clements to CBS Radio for "The World Tonight", Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Party at Empire Room, Jefferson Hotel - shot of Aaroe with girls, Oct. 8, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Party at Empire Room, Jefferson Hotel - shots of crowd, Oct. 8, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Party - Jefferson Hotel (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - arrival shots, Nov. 20, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - boarding plane, Nov. 19. 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - Capital "Viscount" took group to D.C., Nov. 19, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour departs, July 22, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - group shot in front of airplane, Nov. 19, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - inside plane, Nov. 19, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - presentation of gifts to Lieutenant Governor of Hawaii, Nov. 28, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour - return to Byrd Field, Dec. 5, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour Returns, Aug. 5, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour Party Crowd Shots, June 17, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour Party - Hawaiian Band (really Filipino), June 17, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Hawaiian Tour Party - "Hawaiian" Hostesses (In totem pole order: Sandy Wicker, Pat Cuicci, Hilda Flacke, Christine Brooking, and Jeanne Jay), June 17, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Hawthorne Cities Service Station Opening, Oct. 20, 1961 (Box 4)
    - Katie Heinz with Pontiac winning salesmen, Apr. 22, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Heritage Homes on WRVA Theatre Marquee, Nov. 22, 1960 (Box 4)
    - High's Ice Cream window display, Feb. 19, 1959 (Box 4)
    - Frances Hollans and Susan Hollans on telephone for "Open for Opinion" story in Virginia Foodsman Magazine, Aug. 19, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Irby Hollans at 1958 State Fair of Virginia, Sept. 19-27, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Irby Hollans with Dewey Brazell, Richmond District Sales Manager for Purina, John Marshall Hotel, Jan. 9, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Irby Hollans with Robert A. Cook, Adv. and Sales Mgr., Virginia Metal Products Company, Orange, Virginia (Profile), Mar. 22, 1962 (Box 4)